An unfamiliar ceiling.
知らない天井だ。
This is... a hospital? I'm alive?
ここは…病院？僕は生きているのか。
Shinji Ikari, all physical examination results are within normal range. You've been cleared for discharge.
碇シンジ、身体検査の結果は全て正常値です。退院許可が出ました。
After analyzing the combat data from Unit-01, we've discovered something intriguing.
初号機との戦闘データを分析した結果、興味深いことが判明した。
The synchronization rate peaked at 41.3 percent. An astounding figure for the Third Child.
シンクロ率は最大で41.3パーセントに到達。サードチルドレンとしては驚異的な数値だ。
However, the data during the berserk state was unrecordable. All monitors went off the scale.
しかし暴走時のデータは記録不能でした。全てのモニターが振り切れています。
Starting today, you'll be living here. I'm Misato Katsuragi. Nice to meet you.
今日からあなたはここで暮らすことになるわ。葛城ミサトよ、よろしくね。
I'm going to live with the NERV Director of Operations?
ネルフの作戦部長と一緒に住むんですか？
Don't be so formal. You can't do anything on your own, can you?
堅いこと言わないの。あなた、一人じゃ何もできないでしょ？
Analysis of the Angel's tissue shows that 99.89 percent of its composition is identical to humans.
使徒の体組織を分析したところ、構成物質の99.89パーセントが人間と同一でした。
In other words, Angels and humans may share a common origin?
つまり、使徒と人間は同じ起源を持つ可能性があるということか。
That information is classified top secret. Record it only in the MAGI system.
その情報は最高機密とする。MAGIシステムにのみ記録を残せ。
Commander Ikari, the committee is requesting a report on the Third Child's aptitude.
碇司令、委員会から第三の少年の適性について報告を求められています。
No issue. That boy has no choice but to pilot the Eva.
問題ない。あの子には、エヴァに乗る以外の選択肢はない。
Why did I get in the Eva? Was it because I wanted Father's approval?
僕はなぜエヴァに乗ったんだろう。父さんに認めてもらいたかったから？
I mustn't run away. I mustn't run away. I mustn't run away.
逃げちゃだめだ。逃げちゃだめだ。逃げちゃだめだ。
Starting tomorrow, you'll report to NERV headquarters. You are now officially an Eva pilot.
明日からネルフ本部に通ってもらうわ。あなたは正式にエヴァのパイロットよ。
Ikari, you will undergo a pilot aptitude evaluation and basic training.
碇君、あなたにはパイロットとしての適性検査と基礎訓練を受けてもらいます。
Adjusting LCL concentration inside the entry plug. Beginning neural connection test.
エントリープラグ内のLCL濃度を調整。神経接続テストを開始します。
Synchronization rate, stable. No issues. Shinji Ikari, certified as Eva Unit-01's designated pilot.
シンクロ率、安定。問題ありません。碇シンジ、エヴァ初号機専属パイロットに認定。